A Guide to the W. Graham Claytor Papers, 1912-1964
Special Collections, Virginia Tech
- Wo-Wz (Box-folder 6-6)
  - Woods, James P., 1938
  - Woodward, J. B., 1953
  - Woodyard, Henry C., 1947
  - Wright, Frederick A., 1940
  - Wylie's Fishing Calculator, 1944
  - Wysor, Frank, 1950-1951
- X-Z (Box-folder 6-7)
  - YMCA, 1948-1949
  - Zapp, L. M., 1936-1942
  - Ziegler, William Jr., 1948
  - Zimmerman, Laura V., 1938